Hey there.
Well, good morning.
I hope you're doing well.
Hey, kid.
Don't go that way.
If you value your life at all,
don't go any further down that road.
Got it?
An evil demon lives down that way.
A demon?
That's right.
He's a monster who's called Bipolar Jugo.
See that village over there?
He did that years ago.
People are still afraid to live there.
No one that I've ever heard of has gotten
close to him and come back alive.
I'm telling you for your own good,
please turn back!
Well, well.
You followed me home, huh?
Sorry, little guy.
You can't come in.
You can never come inside here.
Now go on.
Get out of here.
Come on, go back home.
Don't come near me.
I'll kill you!
Anyone who comes in here, they'll go!
Who is it?
Don't come near me.
Hey, get out of here.
Go away!
Go, or I'll kill you.
I'll kill you!
Is that what you want?
I'm impressed.
You're very strong.
I almost thought you were going to get me.
Who are you?
Why are you here?
I'm Kimimaro.
The reason I came here was to find you.
Tell me, would you like to come join Lord
Orochimaru?
There are many others like you and me
there.
Outcasts, exiles, all alone just as you
are right now.
If you join us, you won't have to be alone
anymore.
No, I can't.
You don't understand.
I'm not well.
I can't control myself.
There's no telling when I'll try to kill
the people around me.
No, you can't kill me.
I'm not as weak as that.
You're not?
You mean you're not afraid of me?
No, Jugo.
Not at all.
If you start to lose control, then I'll be
your cage.
As long as I'm by your side, then your
soul will remain free.
What?
You can actually do that?
That's right.
I'm simply going to take the enzyme from
your body and absorb it into mine.
And then exactly like you, I'll have the
power of the Curse Mark.
Wait, hold on.
The Curse Mark isn't compatible with all
who absorb it.
If it isn't compatible
with you... I know.
If it doesn't, then I will die.
If you know that, then you can't do this.
It's part of the treatment for both of us.
The disease I carry is slowly eating away
my body.
But if your Curse Mark works, it could
slow the disease's progress indefinitely.
Your power could save me, Jugo.
Please, Jugo, don't worry about me.
I'll be just fine.
We're best friends, after all.
I'm absolutely sure there's no way your
power would reject me.
Kabuto-sensei, it's as I thought,
isn't it?
I wasn't chosen... once again.
Save your strength.
You've served your function well,
Kimimaro.
It's not the Sound Ninja Five anymore.
But still, I... I
haven't... Don't worry.
Your replacement has already been found.
He has a mark equal in power to your Earth
Curse Mark.
He's been given the Heaven Curse Mark.
On top of that, he has the Kekei Genkai.
Kekei Genkai... Kekei Genkai...
Kekei Genkai... I wonder
which one of you is stronger.
Now, now, calm down.
No sense in getting agitated.
Kabuto-sensei...
Tell me truthfully, how much time do you
think I have left?
Relax.
Don't try and talk.
I've been wondering.
There must be a purpose for people being
born into this world.
Why are we here?
What does it mean?
I've been thinking about that a lot
lately.
I realize that finding our purpose is the
meaning.
That's why we're here.
And the ones who find it...
They're the only ones who are truly free.
Yes, I understand what you're saying.
And meanwhile, as we speak, Lord
Orochimaru is suffering horribly.
In fact, if something's not done soon,
it could be the end of him.
You must ask yourself truthfully,
what should you do, Kimimaro?
What's your purpose, now that you're no
longer of any use as a vessel?
At this moment, a new vessel is on its
way.
But unfortunately, it won't arrive in
time.
It's as you say.
My damaged body is of no use to him as a
vessel for the Transference Jutsu.
That was my purpose.
And it's gone.
What is there left to give my existence
meaning?
I see now what I must do.
I was meant to be the vessel.
I was meant to find the vessel.
And bring it safely here.
Even at the cost of my life.
That is the only way I can repay Lord
Orochimaru for my failure.
The only way to give my worthless
existence some value.
Even so, I still want to tell you my
simple feelings.
The wind of that day blows through me.
I was thrown into the ruins of yesterday.
I laugh with you.
I live in the present.
Even so, the sound of the bells.
My memories.
They must be suffering from you.
Even so, I say goodbye.
Without any reason.
I just want to share it with you.
I realize that we have forgotten that.
Even if I sing a song with you.
We're close.
There's only two of them left.
Against the three of us.
I like those odds.
If we play it right, the
next time we meet them,
we'll be able to wrap
things up once and for all.
I'll say!
Two against three, no sweat!
What do you mean, it's two against three?
Oh, sorry about that, Akamaru.
You're right.
It's two against four.
I like those odds even better.
Wait till they see our new technique.
These clowns won't know what hit them,
right, boy?
Don't worry about a thing.
As soon as we catch
up to them, all I gotta do
is my shadow clone
jutsu, and the show's over!
Well, that's comforting to know.
All the same, we're working as a team
here, right?
Just stick to the plan.
Oh, uh, well, sure.
The most important thing is to at least
get them in range before the sun goes down.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's hit it!
The sun's going down, and still no sign of
Jirobo and Kiramaru.
Must have run into more trouble than they
expected.
Who cares about them?
It's Orochimaru I'm worried about.
It's taken us most of a
whole day, and still only
one-third of the transition
process has been completed.
You're right, it's not good.
At this rate, we just might be too late.
Ah!
I thought I saw someone..
Oh yeah, I see now.
They're not here yet!
Still no sign of Sasuke!яг time's running
out he can't go on like this please my
lord there are many other bodies ready for
you my lord they're not here yet!
still no sign of Sasuke!
You may even use mine, if you want You may
even use mine, if you want No!
It must be Sasuke!
Why do you think I've waited this long?
But you've run out of time!
That old man, the third Hokage,
his jutsu was stronger than we thought!
You can't afford to wait any longer.
If you don't take another body right now,
you'll lose everything!
Everything!
I've chosen several suitable vessels.
I'll go get them ready.
And then, I'll see to Sasuke.
Leave everything to me.
Curse you, old man!
Curse you!
Release!
Alright!
Listen up, all of you!
How would you like to be released from
your imprisonment?
...
Sadly, it's just one of you.
What are you waiting for?
Open this door!
You said you would set one of us free!
Or was that just your way of toying with
us?
And who are you?
I expected the other one.
Well, however...
...
What's going on?
I'm about to be eaten alive!
...
Yes, you will be set free.
And before that, I will grant you one
wish.
...
You used my clan for your experiments.
Let them go.
That's my wish.
Yes, of course.
You may consider it done.
Don't worry, your strength
of spirit was one of the main
reasons I chose you, and I'd
be foolish to let it go to waste.
Your residual aura will live on in me.
Well, then.
I thank you.
So it's done.
And now it will be a few years before we
can transfer again.
But next time...
Hold on a second.
Are we almost there?
No.
We still have a ways to go.
But take a look.
And of course, now that we need him,
there's no sign of Jirobo or Kitomaru.
Sorry, just us.
Who needs those two?
I can handle these guys myself.
Get ready!
This is for us!
Charge!
From the palm of his hand?
Shadow clone jutsu, huh?
RAKZENGEN!
Caught my arm!
Just when I... How are you supposed to
hit anyone with it if you can't throw it?
TUNNELING BAG!
They maneuvered SACCON right in front of
you, blocking my view.
They were aiming for me the whole time.
So what?
You think that's gonna do you any good?
No!
Uh... Uh... Uh...
What hit me?
It's called a shadow possession jutsu.
He's got me pinned down!
Meanwhile...
TAYUYA!
Don't just stand there!
Get that guy!
No!
What are you doing?
Get out of the way!
Can't stop in time!
AAAGH!
Here, catch!
TUNNELING BAG!
Good work, Kiba!
Okay, got it!
You heard him, Shikamaru!
Time to pull out!
Don't worry, I'm coming!
You think it's that easy?!
He's fast!
Akamaru!
Once you set the bombs, get moving!
Don't you mess with me!
Akamaru, no!
That's the last time you'll bark at me,
you mutt!
Hang on!
Kiba!
Akamaru!
I can't see them!
Damn!
You're mine now!
There's no other way.
I'll have to take care of this one.
You take the coffin and carry on with the
mission.
Shikamaru!
Just get going!
What?!
What are you doing here?!
Sorry, Naruto.
It looks like I miscalculated.
Kimimaro...
You are taking too long.
Let's go to the And what of our comrades?
What happened to our other three men?
This from the former members of the Sound
Ninja 5.
No way.
Now you're cheating death?
I understand much more now.
The strength of my
life-force has intensified
since escaping the
prison of human flesh.
I've had a taste of Lord Orochimaru's
magnificent dream.
Orochimaru!
This vessel is an important part of his
dream.
It has the flesh that Lord Orochimaru
desires.
But you have taken too much time
retrieving it.
Another freak to deal with.
He doesn't seem like an ordinary opponent.
We need to buy time and sort out the
situation.
It'd be dumb to confront him
without knowing... Hey, jerk!
I've had just about enough of this
nonsense you're yakking about!
Naruto!
I'm taking Sasuke back now!
Hey, wait a second!
I could end your life right now if I wish
to.
The reason I've
decided to spare you is
because you have a duty
that you must complete.
And my duty... is to deliver that coffin
to Lord Orochimaru intact.
I thought you said it was too late for
that now.
You weren't listening.
I told you that's the body that Lord
Orochimaru desires more than anything else.
It's his next vessel.
Exactly, Tayuya.
And delivering it to him is the only thing
that I can do to please him.
As for those two pieces of garbage... I
leave them to you.
He's taking Sasuke!
Not again!
I gotta go get him!
Just calm down, Naruto!
How can I calm down?!
We're losing him!
He's gonna take Sasuke away from us!
Naruto's right.
Our mission is to find Sasuke and bring
him back to the Leaf Village.
We've got to choose the path that's best
for the mission.
And if we don't... we'll fail.
You rodents!
I'm gonna end this in a flash!
Naruto, listen to me.
I've got a plan.
But you've gotta follow it exactly.
His only good move is that shadow clone
jutsu.
Classic close-range moron.
And that one's a mid-range combat type.
Traps his enemies with a shadow jutsu.
Thinks he's a pretty sharp platoon leader,
huh?
Alright, you got it?
Yeah!
Well, let's get on with it, you wimps!
Ugh!
It's two-on-one!
We've got the advantage!
If we gang up on her, we've got a good
shot.
What do you say, Naruto?
Let's get her!
Huh!
It doesn't matter how many of you there are,
you're still a pair of worthless morons!
Don't be cocky.
We've got teamwork on our side.
We'll show you!
Bring it on!
Now, Naruto!
I'm gonna punch your life down!
I'll see you around!
What the?
That whole thing was a trick!
Teamwork, my foot, you dirty, conniving
little weasels!
Nice try!
You sure talk a pretty big game, but
you fell for the oldest trick in the book.
You fool!
You got some nerve!
Oh well.
At least I bought enough time for my
friend to get away.
Hey, remember this.
A person's jutsu isn't his only weapon.
Shikamaru!
I'm counting on you!
When Tai Yuya comes back, I'll have to
kill her.
Hold it right there!
Hey!
Let's see.
How shall I destroy you?
Interesting.
Those eyes.
It seems this one possesses an unusual
chakra.
Tell me what Orochimaru is planning to do!
And why the heck's he trying to get Sasuke
so bad?
Lord Orochimaru has already acquired the
immortality jutsu.
But a vast amount of
time is required to obtain
every jutsu and everything
he wants from this world.
So what?
What does that have to do with Sasuke?
Just because he is immortal doesn't mean
his body can maintain itself forever.
So before his flesh
decays, a strong, new
body must be made
into a vessel for his soul.
Are you saying... that he's gonna use
Sasuke's body?
That's right.
Precisely.
No!
Not Sasuke!
I won't let you do it!
You idiot!
You really think sending that little
shrimp will stop anything?
Besides, just think about what's happened
to your team up to this point.
You probably had to sacrifice
one member each time
you faced an obstacle just
so you could keep moving.
I mean, what the heck is so special about
this Sasuke guy anyway?
How many are you gonna lose just to save
this one insignificant shinobi?
You're pretty dumb for a leader.
You got a point there.
You see, this mission we're on is my first
one as platoon leader.
And it's pretty nerve-wracking to see your
comrades whittled down like this.
To be honest, I don't know if the
decisions I made were the right ones.
As platoon leader, I'm responsible for the
safety of my men.
You would think I'd value
the lives of my four teammates
over the life of one guy
who's been taken prisoner.
It's a dangerous mission,
and if I decided to
scrap it, I'd have been
playing by the book.
Of course.
Then why didn't you scrap it?
It's kinda funny.
The world doesn't seem to play by the book
very often, does it?
Besides, there isn't a single person in my
platoon who would ever stop fighting and
abandon a friend who had been captured by
the enemy.
Not even if it meant sacrificing all of
their lives.
That goes for me, too.
Frankly, I'm a lazy,
cloud-watching oaf who's not really
cut out to be a leader or
bark out orders at anyone.
But there is one thing I do pretty darn
well for my teammates.
And that's believing in them.
Listen, I don't look at what I've done as
sacrificing my men.
In fact, I don't even believe that any of
them are dead.
Don't insult my friends, or you'll pay.
I gotcha!
Dang it.
Get ready, Akamaru.
We'll hit him from both sides with fang
over fang.
Let's do it!
Fang over fang!
Summoning jutsu!
That's not good.
Oh well.
I'll play a little melody of death for
you.
Let's do it!
What's with this guy?
What the...
Why, this is perfect, Sakon.
There's one of them for each of us.
Oh...
You're not taking Sasuke anywhere!
There sure is a lot of garbage scattered
around here.
But... trash is just trash, after all.
It simply needs to be cleaned up.
Shut your mouth!
Come, then.
I'm gonna crush you!
Akamaru!
Aha, so you're the real one, huh?
Multiple fists barrage!
Once more!
My brother and I get along really well.
Usually, U-Khan just sleeps inside of me.
But when the moment calls for it,
he comes out to play.
So this is his ability...
He can poke his arms, legs and head out of
anywhere in my body.
...to either attack or defend.
Just like this.
Multiple legs barrage!
Nothing more painful than a three-legged
kick.
Now try this on for some...
Enough, Sakon.
We don't have any time to play around.
Let's wrap this up.
We're going to phase two.
Oh, alright.
You're always so impatient, brother.
I gotcha.
You're thinking the same.
And those horns aren't just for display,
aren't ya?
You're right.
As soon as that other guy popped out,
his chakra increased tenfold.
Things seemed hopeless before,
but now we're really screwed.
What are you saying?
You're telling me you want to try that?
We can't, Akamaru.
There's nobody here to back us up.
It'd be way too dangerous.
You understand, don't you?
If we whip out that jutsu, we'll use up
what little chakra we have left.
And when it's over, we won't be able to
move.
If we miss, we'll have died for nothing.
Akamaru...
So this is her melody of death.
...
...So she controls
him with that flute.
...
He's not dead!
Ok, you're dead!
That's a good thing.
OK, you're dead!
Oh, darn it!
She kept getting further away.
What am I going to do?
What do I do?
Oh man, this is not good.
I must be a lousy master for you to bite
me like that.
Okay, Akamaru.
It's just like you said.
We're all out of options.
Wolf fang over fang it is.
Now, Akamaru!
Dynamic marking!
What kind of cheap trick is that?
Okay, we're good to go!
Inuzuka Style!
Man Beast Transformation Combo!
Two-Headed Wolf!
All of that flourish and it's nothing but
a big slobbering mongrel.
What could that mud possibly do?
Take this!
The drool!
Sack on you, idiot!
On your right!
Son of a...
Wolf fang over fang!
Heh, how'd you like that?
Wolf fang over fang's
revolution speed is so
intense, we can't see
anything while we're attacking.
But it'll cut you even without direct
contact.
And if it hits you, you'll be ripped to
shreds.
Huh?
Careful, kid.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
This is perfect.
We were just thinking it'd be a good idea
to separate.
What the hell?
He's split in two!
It's true.
If we had taken the full brunt of that
attack, it would have been bad.
But now the real battle begins.
Damn it!
Yeah, I know, Akamaru.
Only one more chance for wolf fang over
fang.
The next shot will be our last.
This time they're going down.
Wolf fang over fang!
It's no use hiding.
I told you, we're not using our eyes.
We marked you earlier on, so now we can
track you just by scent.
Summoning jutsu!
Rashomon!
Impressive.
Rashomon is our greatest defense for Lord
Orochimaru.
And for him to dent it like
that... But it doesn't matter.
This is the end!
Akamaru!
No!
You were trying to protect me!
He did it again!
My eyes!
Damn it!
This is worse than the last time!
It's... some sort of acid!
My eyeballs feel like they're burning!
Where'd the other one go?
Boo.
Looking for someone, kid?
Go wash your eyes in that river.
I'll take care of the rest.
Use it, 가난 파근.
A unique ability I know.
Helps with assassination.
A sharp sense of smell and a set of claws
aren't gonna be enough to beat me.
Face it, you're in over your head,
little dog.
You know that the network in
our bodies through which chakra
passes is deeply interwoven
with our organs, do you not?
Do you know that the network
in our bodies through which
chakra passes is deeply interwoven
with our organs, do you not?
The cells that make up our organs.
The cells that make up those tissues.
Even within each individual protein,
the very building blocks of our cells.
Once in stage two, I'm able
to use chakra to dismantle
and reconstruct these
cells and proteins at will.
Breaking my body down into tiny particles,
I seep into my opponent.
Then return to my original form inside
their body.
Akamaru!
I'm... sorry, Akamaru.
But... I think this time we're sunk,
old friend.
My cells are swimming freely throughout
your body.
I can even generate parts that are solely
yours.
In other words, we're slowly fusing
together.
We'll be sharing a body.
Sharing?
A body?
That's right.
I'm going to snuff out your life as only I
can.
By eradicating all the cells in your body
from the inside out.
I see.
In that case...
What if I do this?
Then what happens?
Suicide?
You're crazy!
Time for you to die.
Are you mad?
What are you doing?
It hurts, doesn't it?
Well, come on.
I know one way to stop the pain.
Sure.
You're just an alligator who's רק за
That's not enough blood for a Fatal Blue.
Who cares anymore if we're less than
family?
Amateallu...
That's not enough blood for a Fatal Blue.
I happen to think I can be a better
valiant of our family here.
Where is he?
The little brat?
So, he ran away and left his little doggy
behind.
A logical decision, but pretty
cold-blooded even for me.
What?
No, it can't be!
It's okay.
He's still breathing.
What a relief.
Good boy, Akamaru.
You really gave it your all.
Thanks to you, we were able to stall the
enemy.
We beat him up pretty good, too.
You rest now.
You've done enough, boy.
I'll kill you!
Hey!
Sakon!
Where are you?
Yeah, yeah.
I hear you.
Stop shouting.
My head's already beating like a gong.
Huh?
Brother!
Right now, all I want to do is find that
brat and tear him to pieces.
But that will have to wait, because now
it's time for me to rest.
If you find him or that mutt, keep them
alive.
I'll kill them when I wake up.
Understood?
You've got a deal, brother.
Only...
We'll do the killing part together.
Yeah!
Now behold... the Will-O-Dance!
Huh?
...What is going on?
Hey, you!
What's going on here?
You're not in any sort of state!
Well, it was you and me!
Really?
What the heck is he?
Bones sticking out of him like a
porcupine!
How does he do that?
Won't be long now.
He's gonna use his own bone as a sword?
It's no use.
This is no ordinary bone.
It's of the highest density, as hard as
tempered steel.
So what?
I'm still gonna break every bone in or out
of your body!
You think you know the limits of my
powers, do you?
I have five dances in my repertoire.
You've only seen one.
Yeah, whatever!
All right, if that's what you want.
I'll let you have it.
Next I'll show you the Camellia Dance.
Come...
What are you waiting for?
Bring it on!
I can smell them... coming this way.
They're close...
I left a trail of blood leading right to
me.
Well, Akamaru, that trick
bought us some time, but it
looks like I may have gotten
a little carried away with it.
That scent... wait a minute.
Why?
What the hell would they be doing here?
I don't know what's going on, but one
thing's for sure.
We gotta beat it.
Fast.
No way.
I'm too dizzy.
Lost too much blood.
Afraid I'm in no better shape than you
are, boy.
Sorry, Akamaru.
So he's traveling by water now,
huh?
What a clever boy.
What a drag.
It's over.
There's nowhere to run this time.
You're trapped like a rat.
Gotta admit, that wasn't bad.
Timing was perfect.
You got all three of them right where you
wanted them.
That's quite a tricky tune.
Something like that must take a lot of
practice.
It does, actually.
So you figured out I was manipulating them
with my flute.
You're not as dumb as you look.
Not that it'll do you any good.
No.
Knowing what I've been doing isn't the
same as knowing how to stop me.
You've got a point there.
I never was very musical.
Just asked my mom and dad.
With that flute, she can manipulate her
buddies like puppets.
That song's comprised of
sequences of modulated sound
waves, each sequence
controlling a specific movement.
Great, Shikamaru.
You can analyze it fine, but what are you
going to do to counteract it?
She's right.
The fact remains that I have no ear for
music.
No one's ever heard this song and lived.
Here's the finale, 9th passage.
Demon pizza.
Revolution.
She changed the tune.
Here they come!
What's happening?
What's he doing?
Wait for it!
The instant he realizes my material ghosts
are about to attack, he evades them.
He's smarter than I thought.
But...
I had to use almost all my paper and smoke
bombs back there.
And all I managed to do was hide...
that white thing.
It took a bite of my physical energy.
That shuriken passed right through him.
These things are more like apparitions
with very little mass.
They're chakra itself, but with an
appetite.
Probably some kind of chakra that draws
its form from eating mental energy.
That's why they crave physical energy.
It keeps them stable.
If I scuffle with those
hungry chakra much
longer, I won't be able
to build up my own chakra.
They're pretty dangerous.
A ninja who can create special chakra like
me?
She must be using some obscure ninjutsu.
Which means I should
leave those ghost things
alone and concentrate on
the one controlling them.
The quickest way would be to go and stop
the sound of her flute.
But with those things around, it would be
impossible to get close enough.
Okay then.
The next best option would be to capture
those three with my shadow possession jutsu.
But that's not gonna happen, since they
never attack me at the same moment.
If I let even one escape, he'd get to me,
and that would be it.
Game over.
She hasn't left me any openings on either
offense or defense.
Heh.
She must be a pretty good shogi player.
Let's see.
My remaining ninja tools are
twelve kunai knives, nine shuriken,
thirty-six feet of wire, one flash
bomb, and one paper bomb.
Heh.
Oh man.
It's like playing shogi without any
bishops or rooks.
There's no use hiding.
Unless you can predict
these guys' movements,
there's nowhere
you can run, little rat.
And when I find you, I'll break you in
two.
Everything's ready.
The only thing left is to get it over
with.
I've got nine moves.
I've gotta win by then.
That's one.
Hm?
Oh, please.
My sound jutsu can't be stopped that
easily.
Whatever you've got planned to beat me,
it's not gonna work.
Two.
Hm?
Now he's scampering around like a little
rat.
Where is he?
Three.
Ah!
It can't be.
He could tell their moves by... He's
saying he memorized my finger positions?
There's no way!
That's impossible!
You extend your right index finger and
ring finger.
Then you place the middle finger and pinky
on your left hand the same way.
That sound seems to make the crab man
stand at the ready.
When you press with your right thumb and
index finger, and move your left index
finger and pinky, that causes the big guy
with the club to charge.
While you were wasting all your time
dodging my knife attacks and trying to
locate me, I was observing
each and every one of your
finger moves, and studying
how these thugs reacted to them.
Analyzed and memorized.
Don't even try.
They're bound by my shadow possession
jutsu.
There's one rule of shogi that I always
enjoyed the most.
Whenever you capture
one of your enemy's pieces,
you can turn around
and use it as your own.
From here on, I attack.
I'll use your own three pieces to hunt you
down.
What do you have to say about that?
Shouldn't you be a bit more worried?
You could at least pull a knife or
something.
This flute is my only weapon.
I told you.
Not one person who's heard the sound of
this flute has survived, idiot.
You've got a lot of confidence.
Dispel!
What was all that about using my own
pieces against me, loser?
It's my move now, you rat!
What the...
Shadow possession success!
What did I tell you?
I'd hunt you down using your own pieces.
I used them all right.
Your three pawns were just the bait I
needed.
In any good strategy, the first attack's
always a fake out.
The tactic is to score on the second move.
You bastard!
Yep.
There's no other way.
Now that it's come to this, I'll need to
summon more power.
I didn't think I'd need to go to second
state with a chump like him.
It ticks me off.
But I've got to admit, for a little punk,
this guy was pretty impressive.
...You might have thought you
were pretty sharp as a fighter...
...but from here on, things won't go
according to your plan!
What is she?
...
No way!
Is she strong enough to force herself out
of the Shadow Possession jutsu?
What's up with this tremendous chakra?
My jutsu is gonna fall apart.
I can't worry about conserving chakra.
I have to use my other jutsu.
Ninja Art, Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
Is it choking my body with that shadow?
It feels just like I'm being grabbed by a
real hand.
I am not letting you beat me!
Darn it!
She's got incredible strength!
At this distance, I can't hold onto her!
Take this!
Demon Flute, Chains of Fantasia!
This is bad.
Is this... a genjutsu?
What's he trying to do?
This is bad.
I can't hold onto her!
My body... I can't move!
When I'm at second state, my flute can
unleash all kinds of genjutsu.
Of all of them, this one's particularly
appropriate for that rat.
That's because...
This genjutsu paralyzes its prey and traps
it like vermin.
Tell me, how's it feel to be the one tied
up?
Die, little rat!
How did you... What?
He broke his own finger with this shadow?
The pain it caused must have broken the
genjutsu!
This whole time, he kept pretending to be
trapped by the jutsu!
I already told you this.
The first attack's always a fake.
Its basic strategy, the second move,
wins the match.
You might have noticed my second move was
a little different from before.
With the shadow-strangled jutsu,
the closer I am to my opponent,
the stronger my hold on him will be.
Darn it!
I got careless and came too close!
No, that's not what did it.
Shouldn't you be a bit more worried?
You could at least pull a knife or
something.
This flute is my only weapon.
I told you, not one person who's heard the
sound of this flute has survived, idiot!
So that's why...
Exactly.
The reason I threw my last kunai knife
right in front of you, I missed on purpose.
You said you didn't have any
other weapons, so I knew all
along that you would pick
it up and come closer to me.
I'll give you credit.
You're a lot smarter than I thought.
And a lot more persistent.
On top of that, I'm a nice guy.
Well, my name is...
Most of the time.
You'll have to excuse my bad manners.
I'm not normally in the habit of slugging
a lady.
But then, looking at you, you don't really
fall into that category, do you?
So I guess it's okay.
You may have escaped my genjutsu,
but don't let it go to your head!
You're still a worm!
She's not completely immobilized by my
shadow possession.
Ugh... I've got to
make this count!
Just a little more...
Ugh...
Even at this range...
With her bound up as
tight as I can make it,
she's still got enough
chakra to push back.
Got to keep the pressure on.
Let up for a second and I'll get hammered!
That's it.
If this jutsu doesn't finish it once and
for all...
Ugh...
Ugh... Ugh... Ugh... Ugh...
Ugh... Well, I've got to go, or
I'm really going to be in trouble!
Ugh... Ugh... Ugh!
Ugh...!
A little pause... and we are back.
This guy... he's incredible!
All those shadow clones, and not one of
them got through!
It's come at last.
The moment I've been waiting for.
The first step toward achieving Lord
Orochimaru's design.
Sasuke!
Hey, Sasuke!
What are you hanging out with these losers
for?
Come on!
Let's go home now!
Talk to me!
What?
Have you gone deaf or something?
Hey, wait!
Sasuke!
It's no use.
Now die!
Sasuke!
Who's this?
In his eye!
The rejuvenated Leaf Village's handsome
devil!
Rock Lee!
Uchi pro!
But what about your injuries?
Do not worry about me, Naruto!
Go get Sasuke!
Really?
Are you sure?
Go on, get going!
I can take care of things here.
This one's strong.
Good.
Okay, but just be careful, will ya?
He uses his own bones for weapons!
His bones?
Interesting.
Watch yourself.
This guy's strength is beyond belief!
Finally!
Then what're you waiting for?
Go!
Thumbs up, Naruto!
Remember?
You gave it to Sakura!
You made her a promise!
I'm gonna bring Sasuke back home no matter
what!
And that's a promise of a lifetime!
Do not worry.
I can finish this one!
I promise!
I don't think so.
You die!
I dislike being ignored.
Good luck, Bushy-brow!
Still, no matter how you look at it,
with Sasuke bottled up in that coffin,
there's not a team of genin on Earth that
can take on that bunch and win.
I'm well aware of that.
I'm not a fool.
And that's why I've already taken certain
measures.
Huh?
She's in here!
Guy, what is it?
Did something happen on your mission?
No.
I ran without a hitch.
And then I ran back as swiftly as my feet
could carry me.
Who cares about my mission?
Tell me, how did this surgery go?
I gotta know!
It was successful.
In fact, I've okayed him to start training
tomorrow.
Going easy at first.
Well, he probably should stay in bed,
but you know him.
I'm afraid we have a problem, my lady.
It's Rock Lee!
He's disappeared from his room!
He must have slipped out last night while
I was treating Genma and Raido.
Little fool.
He must have gone after them.
He must have been half delirious.
Instead of his prescription, he took a
bottle of elixir that I'd left in here.
Bottle of... elixir?
Oh, no... Oh, no!
He is too fast!
I cannot land a single kick!
Your agility is impressive, and you have a
most singular style.
Your style's too direct.
Almost obvious.
It's over.
One moment, please!
I am so sorry, but I have to take my
medicine at a certain time.
And that time happens to be now!
Excuse me, it will take just a minute.
To be honest, I never really liked
medicine.
I first noticed this phenomenon on the
night I took Lee to a restaurant to
celebrate his perfecting the reverse
lotus.
Thinking it was water, he drank some
water.
He drank some of my sake.
A teeny-weeny little cup, barely a sip...
That's when things turned really ugly.
What do you mean exactly?
First, there was this ominous silence.
A moment later, the entire restaurant was
a disaster.
As if... as if a tsunami had hit it.
And then... Whatever it is, it is the
worst tasting medicine I have ever...
Strange.
What sort of medicine is it?
It was pure destruction.
The likes of which I've never seen!
And the older, the better.
What are you staring at?
You stupid jerk!
I-I-I-I-I...
Don't-Don't move, bronzy!
I-I-I... I knew then
what Lee was.
A natural-born master.
A master of the DRAGON FIST!
If you will not make the first move, then
I will just have to bring the fight to you!
His style of attack is fairly direct.
What would you do that for?
I am enjoying the springtime of my youth!
His moves are so unorthodox.
But more than anything, he's fast!
I am in the prime of my youth and taking
the most of it!
This is very hard to idiot.
I will make you pay for the last time!
I will have you pay for this time and I
will make you pay for this time again!
I will be watching you for the next time!
And that's it!
I will get you, trainer!
I can't read his movements.
For him to land an attack on me?
That's quite the Taijutsu.
No other choice.
My true abilities lie within my bones.
I'm sure the little clone brat must have
told you before he left.
I think it's time we sobered you up.
Sober who up?
Do I look drunk to you?
Well, whatever you are, I'll snap you out
of it.
I said I'm not drunk!
In the first place, I'm not even of age!
The underage ninja should not partake in
drinking sake!
Unorthodox, is it not?
This is my kekkei genkai.
He wasn't able to scamper off too far with
that wound of his.
That's it.
I can't go any further.
Are you kidding me?
He's already caught up?
Then wait.
My head is pounding like a drum.
And why is my face bleeding?
It seems I really was drunk after all
then.
What has happened to you?
So, your medicine has finally worn off.
You're looking at my kekkei genkai.
Kekkei genkai?
My kekkei genkai freely controls my
osteoblasts and osteoclasts.
It allows me to alter the concentration of
calcium and form new bones altogether.
Normally, the human body contains 206
bones.
But in my case, that number is somewhat
more negotiable.
Are those really human bones?
Very well!
Behold, my large dance.
Ah!
I've had it!
Just a little bit further!
You piece of garbage!
His scent... he's moving away.
That was close.
What was?
But how did you... I
knew that it would work.
Hehehe.
My jacket!
You're so used to your own smell,
you didn't even notice it on the wind.
So you were skulking around in my jacket
to cover up your scent.
You seem to know a lot about tracking.
No wonder I couldn't smell you.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised,
right?
Seriously, how in the
world am I supposed to
keep track of somebody
who can split in half?
Well, come on then.
I don't know.
Please, wait.
From now on, we play for keeps.
My role now is to stall this person as
long as possible.
I would rather not resort to more powerful
attacks.
They will only leave me vulnerable to
defeat.
But my enemy is a formidable one.
I will have to reveal my secret technique
to best him.
Here I come!
I just had surgery, so I am not at my
best.
But if I only open the first gate,
the gate of opening, I should be alright.
The first gate, gate of opening!
Open!
Primary slowness!
The bone absorbed the impact of my kick!
Your speed is impressive.
But this is over now.
Dammit, I'm racking my brain here.
Why can't I come up with anything?
I'm at the end of my rope.
I can't hold on any longer.
You're staring death in the face.
Shouldn't you be screaming for mercy or
something?
Now die!
You're mine!
You're gonna die, kid!
Wipe that grin off your face!
What the hell?
Who are you?
Allies of the Leaf Village.
Where's Shinobi?
The sand.
Sand Ninja?
Am I still drunk or something?
Digital shrapnel!
No!
He
fired the bones from his fingertips?
Impulsive, aren't you?
You're different.
When you fought against me, you had much
more agility and sharpness.
I figured you would say that.
I am not the kind of person who holds a
grudge, even so.
Because of you, I've had a fairly tough
time of it.
Really?
Anyway, why have you come here?
I owe the Leaf...
I owe the Leaf a great debt.
Sasuke!
추천의 차례 I had heard something about how our
Village had finally made up with you
traitors, but I didn't expect you to
change sides so quickly.
It's not like we just attacked the Leaf
Village for kicks, you know.
We were following orders.
That's all.
Just like we're doing on this mission.
Hmm.
I get it.
The fifth Hokage sent them.
She saved our butts.
By the way, you seem a lot dumber than the
last time our paths crossed.
Huh?
Hmm.
So are you gonna give up again this time?
Go ahead, I'll take care of this for you.
Well, I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm not about to give up.
And besides, a real man doesn't let a
woman do his fighting for him.
Hmm.
Huh.
Still being all macho with the man and
woman stuff?
You talk tough, but I know it's just an
act.
Idiot.
So this time you're on the Leaf side,
huh?
You guys are all over the place,
aren't ya?
The sound of the flute summons her
genjutsu.
I got it.
Cyclone Sight Jutsu!
She's deflecting the
sound of the flute and
nailing our opponent
with a physical attack.
She can attack and defend at the same
time.
That's a pretty handy jutsu to have.
It's like that girl was born to fight me!
Well, I don't see him.
I guess Ukon must have taken him out
already.
So you fight with puppets?
Behind you!
It's no use!
I can't move!
What is this guy?
He's all yours, Sakon!
Finish him!
I'll get you!
Be careful!
He's about to try and enter your body and
combine with it!
It's too late!
I guess that jutsu of yours doesn't really
work on puppets, does it?
This one's a puppet too!
Fair warning, we Sand Ninja aren't
pushovers, like our friends from the Leaf.
Oh, and standing as close as you are to my
friend the Black Ant?
Big mistake.
I hated going up
against the Sand Ninja as
enemies, but as allies,
they're pretty amazing.
That hurt.
You take over, brother.
Let me rest at this body a little bit
first.
You're so pathetic, Sakon.
Just who are these freaks?
This is their most dangerous ability.
I can't believe you let that puppet get
you off guard.
Well, you can be sure I won't.
Its puny power and speed are nothing
special.
It'll take more than this toy to stop me.
His wounds are already back to normal.
That healing ability is unbelievable.
I'm not usually the one who turns into the
main body.
It's hard to move like this.
This isn't the kind of enemy you can beat
head to head.
Back down and we'll regroup.
I can't back down when they show me no
respect.
My Black Ant puppet isn't designed to be
used on offense.
Its usual function is trapping people.
But when the Black Ant is paired with the
Crow, it makes a deadly attack combination.
Hey, you punks!
Let me out of here!
Can you hear me?
Secret Black move!
Iron Maiden!
I'm going to kill you!
She must be hiding around here.
I told you to explain the situation to me,
that's all.
You have no idea what kind of powers I
have.
If she thinks she can hide
from me, but stay close
enough so the sound of
her flute can still reach me...
She's mistaken.
All right!
Summoning Blade Dance!
Slash!
All right.
I'm far enough away.
It's time for my Genjutsu.
Huh?
Ah!
I'm going to kill you!
How was that?
It's finished.
Huh?
She doesn't mess around, huh?
She's as subtle as a rhino.
She might even be scarier than my mom.
Pretty good, huh?
Oh well.
Heh.
This time I guess I should be grateful
she's so scary.
I'll handle this.
No, please!
Just back me up!
I've got sand in my mouth!
Will you please let go of me?
You're not doing anything in your present
state.
I've got this.
You're Gaara of the Desert.
You wield sand.
Hence the name.
That sand is a strong defense.
But he's definitely not the close combat
type.
Getting close will probably be difficult,
though.
I'm going to kill you!
Hmm.
DJ, don't fret now!
His attacks and defense are as one.
All achieved with sand.
But the sand which
he can wield is probably
limited to the amount
that fits in that gourd.
Why else would you go through the trouble
of lugging it around?
Sand shower.
What a surprise.
If I need more sand, I can easily use the
earth we're standing on to make more.
Of course.
Now I see.
All of this time he has been feeding his
own sand into the ground.
And using it to grind up the stones and
minerals in the earth beneath us.
Creating new sand.
Gaara of the Desert.
They do not call him that for nothing.
Maisie.
You did it!
Almost.
Sand burial!
Ah!
Impossible!
That sure was a lot of pressure.
If I hadn't grown a membrane
of bone underneath my
skin, I would have been
crushed beyond recognition.
More bones.
He's a monster.
A freak.
Well, he certainly is a nuisance.
I underestimated you.
But that's the last time I'll get caught
in your sand.
Sand tsunami!
You will pay for this!
But of course, you'll pay for this!
To think that he could change the terrain
itself!
He is so powerful!
He is even stronger than when we fought
each other!
Well, surely this time...
Why won't he give up?
What?
I'm still alive.
If so, there must be a reason for it.
We descend upon the village hidden in the
mist under the cover of night.
We all feel the sting of the reaper.
And the recent betrayal.
Well, tonight they'll see savagery like
they've never known!
Show these scum the ferocity of our clan
down to every last man, woman and child!
What are you waiting for, Kimimaro?
Get going already!
I'm not sure what to do.
What's there to think about?
Go down to the village of the mist and kill
every single person... you come across!
Just follow your instincts.
It'll come to you.
Are you from the mist village?
No.
I... I see.
Sorry.
This is the closes door.
Haku... I'll go get some
drinks on before now.
No, it's nothing.
I feel a bit like...
Sorry, Zabuza.
We don't have time for daydreaming.
Better get on with your life.
Right.
His eyes were in the defect.
It was only so before I met Zabuza.
Ahh!
One moment!
Just a moment.
A little pause... and we are back.
What a bunch of idiots.
They understand nothing other than the
sword.
The days are gone when a horde of savages
could go slaughtering all in their path.
Brute strength is nothing in the face of a
regimented military.
These fools are rushing to their death.
I'm alone.
Again.
Why are you here?
Why are you blooming in a place like this?
How come you won't answer me, huh?
Oh, so you're going to ignore me too,
then.
Who cares anyway?
It's not like anyone will see you here!
That will do.
Maybe, just maybe, there is no purpose in
life.
But if you linger a while longer, you might
discover something of value in this world.
Like how you discovered that flower.
Or how I discovered you one fateful night.
Come, it's time to go.
I was put on this Earth to protect Lord
Orochimaru and his ambitions.
I must welcome them, Atellans.
I was祈。」 Ganon!
As the last자 Is that the best you can do
with your ultimate defense?
King Galgal Gear Al lean?
w measures.
I'm a libraries of death.
Alexander Algo.
I see.
An armor-like shell of sand.
He is not your only opponent!
That might have been the end.
If Gaara had not intervened...
My body is still too weak.
I am only a burden to him like this.
I'm tired of that sand.
Very well, Gaara.
You first.
His spine!
How is it possible?
Clematis Dance!
First, the vine.
Then, the flower.
This bone is my strongest.
It will bore right through you,
defenses and all.
I don't have much time.
My ultimate defense!
Shukaku's shield!
It's so strong.
I took the hardest minerals in the soil I
gathered.
And then I fused them with the sand using
my chakra.
Tell me.
That's a very unusual jutsu.
It's a kekkei genkai, right?
It belonged to the Kaguya.
But now, it belongs to me and me alone.
You're the last of your clan, eh?
Then your clan perishes today.
That might very well be the case.
My body has weakened.
It may not last much longer.
However...
I will still live on.
Because... I am not alone.
You're not alone, you say?
That's right.
My existence has been subsumed into Lord
Orochimaru's ambition.
That means a part of me will survive in
Lord Orochimaru's heart forever.
Orochimaru's brainwashed you well.
You sad little pawn.
I put
a lot into this battle.
Almost out of chakra.
I must make this last thing count.
I will bury you two hundred meters below
the surface of the earth.
Under pressure so great you won't be able
to move a finger.
Imprisoned there till the end of time.
I will destroy you.
Bracken dance.
Thank you, Gaara.
You saved me again.
These powers of yours are truly
remarkable.
Not really.
I'm merely able to make the sand do my
bidding.
It's second nature to me now.
A tenacious opponent, but this time it's
over.
We won't be seeing him again in this life.
Yes, good.
My strength is gone.
We must descend.
I am not his pawn.
He is the one.
The only one who ever gave my life
meaning.
But how could the likes of you ever
understand that?
He is dead.
Can it be?
Kimimaro?
No matter.
He's of no further use to me.
All that matters now is that Sasuke is
coming.
And of his own free will.
Just as I foretold.
Sasuke.
What a sheer luck.
I should have been killed.
No, it was not meant to be.
My sensei has often said to me.
A good ninja always makes his own luck.
That meddlesome mother hen.
Gai-sensei is nothing of the sort.
I am very grateful to you for having saved
my life.
But I warn you.
I will not abide anyone speaking ill of my
sensei.
So you're another one, eh?
Hm?
You have someone in your life whom you
honor and revere so much that every hurt
inflicted on them is inflicted on you as
well.
And the closer they are to you,
the greater the pain.
To feel so strongly for someone you would
fight for them.
And die for them.
You and Naruto Uzumaki have that in
common.
No.
However.
What if this person you honor and revere.
Would even die for as not a virtuous
person?
Impossible!
Such a person would be unworthy of honor
or respect.
No.
Perhaps the companionship of even an evil
person.
Is preferable to loneliness.
Sasuke!
I am in your hands!
No!
Kamehameha!
You are so beautiful.
I don't know everything.
No!
This is the only one!
I want it!
That's my first time.
Shut up.
Stop it.
A little pause... and we are back.